Finding Aid for the Peter H. Prince Papers MS.2921
University of Tennessee Libraries, Special Collections
- Research Files, 1770-2006; I
  - Photographs, 1838-2006 (bulk 1884-2005); J
    - Fairview: William G. Posey Gravesite, 1997 June 1 (Box 28, Folder 75)
    - Fairview: Andrew Jackson Posey Tub Mill, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 76)
    - Fairview: Andrew J. Posey Family, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 77)
    - Fairview: Dad Collins' Store, 1943, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 78)
    - Fairview: Annie Davis Gravesite, 1991 February 16 (Box 28, Folder 79)
    - Fairview: Willis P. Davis, undated (Box 28, Folder 80)
    - Fairview: Willis P. Davis Gravesite, 1991 February 17 (Box 28, Folder 81)
    - Fairview: Annie Davis (a founder of the Great Smoky Mountains National Park), undated (Box 28, Folder 82)
    - Chambers Creek: Samuel S. Collins Gristmill (built 1901), 1913; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 72, Folder 3] (Box 28, Folder 83)
    - Chambers Creek: Chambers Creek Students, 1900, 1996; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 72, Folder 4] (Box 28, Folder 84)
    - Chambers Creek: Chambers Church Baptizing, 1919, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 85)
    - Chambers Creek: Chambers Creek School (1867-1925), 1915, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 86)
    - Chambers Creek: Thomas Grant and Mary Jane (Monteith) Chambers, undated (Box 28, Folder 87)
    - Chambers Creek: Chambers Creek Baptist Church Painting, undated (Box 28, Folder 88)
    - Chambers Creek: Alfred B. Cline (murdered by Bushwhackers), undated (Box 28, Folder 89)
    - Chambers Creek: Maryline Cline Collins (operated grist mill), undated (Box 28, Folder 90)
    - Chambers Creek: Roxie McClure Overshot Mill, 1943; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 72, Folder 5] (Box 28, Folder 91)
    - Chambers Creek: Apple Drying for the Winter, undated (Box 28, Folder 92)
    - Chambers Creek: Granny Does the Churning, circa 1913 (Box 28, Folder 93)
    - Chambers Creek: Lloyd Brooks, undated (Box 28, Folder 94)
    - Chambers Creek: Collinwood, NC, undated (Box 28, Folder 95)
    - Chambers Creek: Henry B. Anthony House, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 96)
    - Chambers Creek: Japan, NC, Post Office, undated (Box 28, Folder 97)
    - Chambers Creek: Japan, NC, Post Office, 1943 May 25, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 98)
    - Chambers Creek: Japan, NC, Post Office, undated (Box 28, Folder 99)
    - Chambers Creek: Samuel S. Collins Grist Mill (built 1901), 1913 (Box 28, Folder 100)
    - Chambers Creek: Zora Collins Chambers Family, 1916, 1997; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 73, Folder 1] (Box 28, Folder 101)
    - Chambers Creek: Chambers Creek Missionary Baptist Church, circa 1943 (Box 28, Folder 102)
    - Chambers Creek: Mary Monteith Chambers, 1939 (Box 28, Folder 103)
    - Chambers Creek: Samuel S. Collins and Maryland Pearson Marriage Certificate, 1892 March 12 (Box 28, Folder 104)
    - Chambers Creek: Chambers Creek Baptist Church Painting, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 105)
    - Trail of Tears: Painting by Robert Lindneux, 2004-2005 (Box 28, Folder 106)
    - Trail of Tears: Tsali (Cherokee Martyr) Shot, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 107)
    - Trail of Tears: Tsali (Cherokee Martyr) Shot, 1996 March 12 (Box 28, Folder 108)
    - Trail of Tears: Tsali (Cherokee Martyr) Shot, undated (Box 28, Folder 109)
    - Trail of Tears: Tsali (Cherokee Hero) Shot, undated (Box 28, Folder 110)
    - Trail of Tears: General Winfield Scott, undated (Box 28, Folder 111)
    - Trail of Tears: Andrew Jackson, undated (Box 28, Folder 112)
    - Trail of Tears: General Winfield Scott, undated (Box 28, Folder 113)
    - Trail of Tears: President Martin Van Buren, undated (Box 28, Folder 114)
    - Bushnell: Ohio Governor Asa S. Bushnell, 1896, 1995, 2005; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 73, Folder 2] (Box 28, Folder 115)
    - Bushnell: Gatlinburg Plaque Commemorating Tsali, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 116)
    - Bushnell: General Winfield Scott, undated; [Folder Found Empty] (Box 28, Folder 117)
    - Bushnell: A. J. Monteith, circa 1934 (Box 28, Folder 118)
    - Bushnell: Cherokee Indian Family, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 119)
    - Bushnell: Roy Stansberry Home, undated (Box 28, Folder 120)
    - Bushnell: Swinging Bridge, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 121)
    - Bushnell: Tuckaseegee, undated (Box 28, Folder 122)
    - Bushnell: Buggy by the River, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 123)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell Missionary Baptist Church, circa 1943; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 73, Folder 3] (Box 28, Folder 124)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell Post Office, undated (Box 28, Folder 125)
    - Bushnell: Students at Bushnell School, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 126)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell School, undated (Box 28, Folder 127)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell School Students, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 128)
    - Bushnell: Edgar Fisher's Store, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 129)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell Swinging Bridge, undated (Box 28, Folder 130)
    - Bushnell: NC 288 and Tennessee & Carolina Southern Railroad, undated (Box 28, Folder 131)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell Hotel, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 132)
    - Bushnell: Ed Welch Home and Overshot Mill, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 133)
    - Bushnell: Bushnell Student, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 134)
    - Bushnell: Columbus Welch Home, 1943 April 26 (Box 28, Folder 135)
    - Bushnell: Bend in the Tennessee River, 1943 May 12 (Box 28, Folder 136)
    - Southern Railway: Cocke Locomotive No. 168, Train 17 at Bushnell, 1903-1913, 1981-2004; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 90, Folder 5] (Box 28, Folder 137)
    - Southern Railway: Murphy Branch Line Timetable, 1929 April (Box 28, Folder 138)
    - Southern Railway: Bushnell Depot, 1917 August 2, 1994; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 73, Folder 4] (Box 28, Folder 139)
    - Southern Railway: Bushnell Trestle, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 140)
    - Southern Railway: Colonel Alexander Boyd Andrews, undated (Box 28, Folder 141)
    - Southern Railway: Richmond & Danville Railroad, 1997; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 73, Folder 5] (Box 28, Folder 142)
    - Southern Railway: Richmond & Danville Railroad Trestle in Governor's Island, NC, 1884, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 143)
    - Southern Railway: Cowee Tunnel, circa 1892, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 144)
    - Southern Railway: Ernest and Gladys Fisher, 1918; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 73, Folder 6] (Box 28, Folder 145)
    - Southern Railway: Bushnell Hotel, Store, and Post Office, circa 1943 (Box 28, Folder 146)
    - Southern Railway: Bushnell Missionary Baptist Church, 1943 April 26 (Box 28, Folder 147)
    - Southern Railway: First Passenger Train in the Great Smoky Mountains National Park, 1889 October 27, 1988-1997; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 74, Folder 1] (Box 28, Folder 148)
    - Southern Railway: Murphy Line No. 18, 1913 (Box 28, Folder 149)
    - Southern Railway: Carolina & Tennessee Southern Section Crew, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 150)
    - Southern Railway: Carolina & Tennessee Southern Railway, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 151)
    - Southern Railway: Locomotive in North Carolina, undated (Box 28, Folder 152)
    - Southern Railway: Big Snowbird Railroad Trestle, 1906, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 153)
    - Southern Railway: Southern Railway Rerouted, 1944 April 28, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 154)
    - Southern Railway: Bushnell Depot, circa 1944 (Box 28, Folder 155)
    - Southern Railway: Lease of Western North Carolina to Richmond & Danville, 1886 (Box 28, Folder 156)
    - Southern Railway: Murphy Division (Jackson County), undated (Box 28, Folder 157)
    - Southern Railway: Western North Carolina Railroad, undated (Box 28, Folder 158)
    - Southern Railway: Jarrett's Station, 1891 (Box 28, Folder 159)
    - Southern Railway: Richmond & Danville Railroad Map, 1887 (Box 28, Folder 160)
    - Southern Railway: Tuckaseegee River Trestle, 1886 (Box 28, Folder 161)
    - Southern Railway: TVA Engineers Inspect New Track, 1944 April 28 (Box 28, Folder 162)
    - Southern Railway: TVA Rerouting to Almond, 1943 (Box 28, Folder 163)
    - Southern Railway: Bridge Removal on Tuckaseegee River, 1944 (Box 28, Folder 164)
    - Southern Railway: New Bridge on the Little Tennessee, 1944 August 23 (Box 28, Folder 165)
    - Southern Railway: Freight in Noland, NC, 1943 April 5 (Box 28, Folder 166)
    - Southern Railway: Relocation to Almond, 1943 March 8 (Box 28, Folder 167)
    - Southern Railway: Bridge Construction on the Little Tennessee, 1943 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 168)
    - Southern Railway: Pier Nantahala Highway Bridge, 1943 September 2 (Box 28, Folder 169)
    - Southern Railway: Nantahala River Highway Bridge, 1944 April 28 (Box 28, Folder 170)
    - Southern Railway: New Southern Railway Tracks, 1944 July 26 (Box 28, Folder 171)
    - Southern Railway: Snowbird Valley Railway, 1905 (Box 28, Folder 172)
    - Southern Railway: Western North Carolina Railroad, undated (Box 28, Folder 173)
    - Southern Railway: Three-Engine Train, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 74, Folder 2] (Box 28, Folder 174)
    - Southern Railway: Cowee Railroad Tunnel (1882-1884), undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 74, Folder 3] (Box 28, Folder 175)
    - Southern Railway: Cowee Tunnel (1882-1884), undated (Box 28, Folder 176)
    - Southern Railway: Murphy Branch Passenger Service, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 177)
    - Southern Railway: Bemis Lumber Company Shay Engine No. 4, undated (Box 28, Folder 178)
    - Southern Railway: Climax Locomotive No. 10, undated (Box 28, Folder 179)
    - Southern Railway: Hall's Station (Murphy Line), 1887, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 180)
    - Southern Railway: Indian Ridge Tunnel, undated (Box 28, Folder 181)
    - Southern Railway: Indian Ridge Tunnel, 1884, 2003; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 74, Folder 4] (Box 28, Folder 182)
    - Southern Railway: Convict Leasing on the Murphy Line, undated (Box 28, Folder 183)
    - Forney Creek: Forney Creek Cascade, 1997 May 18 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Forney Creek: John Monteith Store, 1943, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Forney Creek: Forney's Creek Missionary Baptist Church, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Forney Creek: Forney Creek Cascades, 1908, 1997, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Forney Creek: Forney Creek Cascade (85'), 1991-2005 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Forney Creek: Thomas J. Forney and William A. Erwin, 1838 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Forney Creek: Forney Family Coat of Arms, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Forney Creek: Forney Creek (NC) Postmark, 1908 November 16 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Forney Creek: Forney Railroad Station, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Forney Creek: Southern Railway, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Forney Creek: CCC Camp 413 (est. 1933), undated (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Forney Creek: Forney's Creek School (closed 1939), circa 1930s (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Forney Creek: W. Thomas Woody Mill, circa 1927 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Forney Creek: W. Thomas Woody Tub Mill, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Forney Creek: T. W. Woody Tub Mill, circa 1937 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Forney Creek: The Main Highway to Church, undated (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Forney Creek: Gee (later called Forney), 1908 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Forney Creek: Forney's Creek Baptist Church, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Forney Creek: George Monteith Plowing, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Forney Creek: Mrs. Kelley Cole and Son, 1943, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Forney Creek: CCC Camp 413 (established 1933), undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Forney Creek: Southern Railway Stop on NC 288, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Forney Creek: William Welch Sr. (Haywood County), 1996 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Forney Creek: Horace Kephart, 1904 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Forney Creek: Jesse R. Siler, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Forney Creek: Siler Meadows Copper Mine, 1904 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Lumber Railroad Switchback, 1908, 1997-2002 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Incline at Clingman's Dome, 1910, 1997; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 74, Folder 5] (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Clingman's Dome Logging Camp, 1912; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 75, Folder 1] (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Spruce Log Pile, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Forney, NC, Mill, 1917, 1995; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 75, Folder 2] (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Steam Engine Incline (1910-1924), 1997 April 26 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Junction Camp, NC, circa 1912; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 75, Folder 3] (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Climax Type A Locomotive, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Railroad Incline Engine, 1925 April (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Mess Hall Artifacts (1908-1924), 1997 April 26 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Incline Steam Engine Boiler (1910), 1990 April 15 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Climax Engine Pulling Logs, 1916; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 75, Folder 4] (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Monteith Cabin, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Incline to Clingman's Dome, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Steam Engine Incline (1910-1924), 1997 April 26; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 75, Folder 5] (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Climax Locomotive, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Norwood Lumber Company, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Deserted Mill in Forney, NC, 1939 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: W. T. Woody Tub Mill, undated (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Log Loading, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Bear Creek Railroad Trestle, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Log Loader, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Clingman's Dome Camp Artifacts, 1987 June 6 (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Ghost Railroad, 1987 June 6 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Railroad Engine Brake Shoe, 1987 June 6 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Ground Skidder, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Bear Creek Railroad Incline, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: High Rocks Tower (5190'), undated (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Clingman's Dome Incline Cable (1908-1925), 1996 April 5 (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Cutting Red Spruce, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Incline Boiler, 1987 June 6 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Tank Engine, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Pink Thomason and Dr. E. L. Prince at Junction Camp, 1920; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 76, Folder 1] (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Lawrence Crisp on Steam Incline, 1912 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Steeltrap Creek Railroad Trestle, 1912; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 76, Folder 2] (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Colonel Thomas J. Forney Gravesite, 1995 November 20; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 76, Folder 3] (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Arnold E. Bradshaw Family, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Mrs. Arnold E. (Meeda) Bradshaw, 1991 October 5 (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Arnold E. Bradshaw Home, 1942-1946 (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Norwood Lumber Company: Lula Styles Ballew Family, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Clingman's Dome: General Thomas Clingman Monument, 2005 November 10 (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Clingman's Dome: Dr. Samuel Leonidas Love, 1932, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 68)
    - Clingman's Dome: General Thomas Lanier Clingman, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 76, Folder 4] (Box 29, Folder 69)
    - Clingman's Dome: Samuel Leonidas Love, undated (Box 29, Folder 70)
    - Clingman's Dome: Dr. Samuel L. Love Gravesite, 1996 September 20 (Box 29, Folder 71)
    - Clingman's Dome: General Thomas Lanier Clingman, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 72)
    - Clingman's Dome: General Thomas L. Clingman Gravesite, 1995 October 23 (Box 29, Folder 73)
    - Clingman's Dome: Clingman's Dome Tower (built 1959), 1960 (Box 29, Folder 74)
    - Clingman's Dome: General Thomas L. Clingman Gravesite, 1990 March 31 (Box 29, Folder 75)
    - Clingman's Dome: Observation Tower (1934-1959), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 76)
    - Clingman's Dome: First Tower, 1929 June 9 (Box 29, Folder 77)
    - Clingman's Dome: Plaque at Tower, undated (Box 29, Folder 78)
    - Clingman's Dome: General Thomas L. Clingman Obituary, 1897 November 3; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 76, Folder 5] (Box 29, Folder 79)
    - Clingman's Dome: Thomas Lanier Clingman, 1877 (Box 29, Folder 80)
    - Clingman's Dome: Snowcapped Clingman's Dome, undated (Box 29, Folder 81)
    - Clingman's Dome: Reverend Elisha Mitchell, undated (Box 29, Folder 82)
    - Clingman's Dome: Reverend Elisha Mitchell, undated (Box 29, Folder 83)
    - Clingman's Dome: Mount Mitchell (6684'), 1900 (Box 29, Folder 84)
    - Clingman's Dome: Storm over the Little Tennessee Valley, 1937 January 31; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 77, Folder 1] (Box 29, Folder 85)
    - Clingman's Dome: Clingman's Dome (Myrtle Point), 1926 (Box 29, Folder 86)
    - Clingman's Dome: Wooden Observation Tower, 1934 (Box 29, Folder 87)
    - Clingman's Dome: Tower, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 88)
    - Clingman's Dome: Tower, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 89)
    - Clingman's Dome: Tower, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 90)
    - Noland: Charles J. Harris Gravesite, 1990 March 31 (Box 29, Folder 91)
    - Noland: Charles J. Harris Gravesite, 1995 October 23 (Box 29, Folder 92)
    - Noland: Charles J. Harris Gravesite, 1996 June 12 (Box 29, Folder 93)
    - Noland: Mount Mitchell Railroad, circa 1913, 1997, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 94)
    - Noland: Hydro-Electric Plant, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 95)
    - Noland: Noland Creek, circa 1929 (Box 29, Folder 96)
    - Noland: Noland School, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 97)
    - Noland: Phillip G. Rust Summer Home, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 98)
    - Noland: Phillip Rust Hydro-Electric Plant, 1943, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 99)
    - Noland: Cole Hyatt House, 1943 May 8 (Box 29, Folder 100)
    - Noland: Clinton Lewis Plowing, 1943 May 4 (Box 29, Folder 101)
    - Noland: Pottery Kiln, 1943 April 26 (Box 29, Folder 102)
    - Noland: Rust Home, 1942 September 8, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 103)
    - Noland: Bill Fuller Home, undated (Box 29, Folder 104)
    - Noland: Bill Fuller, 1944 March 1; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 77, Folder 2] (Box 29, Folder 105)
    - Noland: Will Jenkins, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 106)
    - Noland: Gold Mine Branch Community, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 107)
    - Noland: Reverend Evion O. Hall Property, 1943 May 8 (Box 29, Folder 108)
    - Noland: Will Jenkins Home, 1944 March 1 (Box 29, Folder 109)
    - Noland: Evion O. Hall Grist Mill and Power Plant, circa 1930s (Box 29, Folder 110)
    - Noland: Andrew Jackson and Louise Hall, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 111)
    - Noland: Andrew Jackson Hall Reunion, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 112)
    - Noland: Charles J. Harris Photograph and Obituary, 1944 February 15; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 77, Folder 3] (Box 29, Folder 113)
    - Noland: Noland Creek Log Flume, 1906 (Box 29, Folder 114)
    - Andrews Bald: Andrew Thompson Gravesite, 1997 September 15 (Box 29, Folder 115)
    - Andrews Bald: Nathan B. Thompson Gravesite, 1996 April 6 (Box 29, Folder 116)
    - Andrews Bald: Reverend Nathan B. Thompson's Bible (1829), 1996 September 20; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 78, Folder 1] (Box 29, Folder 117)
    - Andrews Bald: Andrew Thompson (lived in Going Snake, Indian Territory; was Kansas, Indian Territory's first Postmaster), 1999; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 77, Folder 4] (Box 29, Folder 118)
    - Andrews Bald: Cabin Dowsing, 1996; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 77, Folder 5] (Box 29, Folder 119)
    - Andrews Bald: Andrews Bald Cabin, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 120)
    - Andrews Bald: Nathan B. Thompson Gravesite, 1996 June 5 (Box 29, Folder 121)
    - Andrews Bald: National Capitol at Tahlequah, 1997 September 14; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 79, Folder 1] (Box 29, Folder 122)
    - Andrews Bald: Andrews Bald Cabin, 1932 September 18; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 79, Folder 2] (Box 29, Folder 123)
    - Andrews Bald: Andrew Thompson, 1999; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 79, Folder 3] (Box 29, Folder 124)
    - Andrews Bald: Andrews Bald Cabin, 1932 September 18 (Box 29, Folder 125)
    - Andrews Bald: James Andrew Thompson Name Authority, 1896; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 79, Folder 4] (Box 29, Folder 126)
    - Charleston Township: Stiles Cemetery, 1987 June 14 (Box 29, Folder 127)
    - Charleston Township: Horace Kephart Memorial, undated (Box 29, Folder 128)
    - Charleston Township: Frye Mountain, 1935 August 14 (Box 29, Folder 129)
    - Charleston Township: Tuckaseegee River Footbridge, 1943 March 23 (Box 29, Folder 130)
    - Epps Springs: Old Swain County Courthouse, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 131)
    - Epps Springs: Ben Lollis with Mule Team, 1943 May 4 (Box 29, Folder 132)
    - Epps Springs: Colonel Thaddeus Bryson, undated (Box 29, Folder 133)
    - Epps Springs: Kelly E. Bennett, undated (Box 29, Folder 134)
    - Epps Springs: Kelly E. Bennett Gravesite, 1996 June 5 (Box 29, Folder 135)
    - Epps Springs: Silas Ball Family, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 136)
    - Epps Springs: Lakeview Road Auto Tunnel, 1973, 1987-1994 (Box 29, Folder 137)
    - Epps Springs: Ben Lollis Home, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 138)
    - Epps Springs: Tuckaseegee River Swinging Bridge, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 139)
    - Epps Springs: Charlie C. McClean Store, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 140)
    - Epps Springs: E. Everett, 2000 August 12 (Box 29, Folder 141)
    - Epps Springs: Epaphroditus Everett, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 80, Folder 1] (Box 29, Folder 142)
    - Epps Springs: Epps Springs Hotel Advertisement, 1907 June 23 (Box 29, Folder 143)
    - Epps Springs: School and Church, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 144)
    - Epps Springs: Indian Boundary, 1996 September 18 (Box 29, Folder 145)
    - Epps Springs: NC 288, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 146)
    - Epps Springs: E. Everett Gravesite, 1996 June 5 (Box 29, Folder 147)
    - Epps Springs: Hanging of Cherokee Andrew Lambert (1887), 2000 August 12 (Box 29, Folder 148)
    - Epps Springs: Jack E. Coburn, undated; [Oversized Materials Removed to Box 80, Folder 2] (Box 29, Folder 149)
    - Epps Springs: Bryson City, 1900 (Box 29, Folder 150)
    - Deep Creek: Thomas Andrew Wiggins Gravesite, 2004 March 21 (Box 29, Folder 151)
    - Deep Creek: Mountain Family, undated (Box 29, Folder 152)
    - Deep Creek: Toms Falls, 1996 June 5 (Box 29, Folder 153)
    - Deep Creek: Juney Whank Falls and Gravesite, 2003 May 24 (Box 29, Folder 154)
    - Deep Creek: Carl Watson House, 1938 March 15 (Box 29, Folder 155)
    - Deep Creek: George Washington Jenkins Place, 1937 May 14 (Box 29, Folder 156)
    - Deep Creek: Jenkins Place Bridge, 1935 October 25 (Box 29, Folder 157)
    - Deep Creek: Bryson Place, 1938 (Box 29, Folder 158)
    - Deep Creek: Deep Creek School Souvenir, 1902 December 4 (Box 29, Folder 159)
    - Deep Creek: Deep Creek School 2nd Grade Certificate, 1880 November 15 (Box 29, Folder 160)
    - Deep Creek: Adolphus Swain Overshot Mill, 1987 October 8 (Box 29, Folder 161)
    - Deep Creek: Ephraim Bumgarner Barn, 1937 May 13 (Box 29, Folder 162)
    - Deep Creek: Jim Bumgarner Pounding Mill, 1935, undated (Box 29, Folder 163)
    - Deep Creek: Jim Bumgarner Pounding Mill, 1935 (Box 29, Folder 164)
    - Deep Creek: Bryson Place CCC Camp 1216, 1935 February 15 (Box 29, Folder 165)
    - Deep Creek: Bryson Place, undated (Box 29, Folder 166)
    - Deep Creek: Ephraim Bumgardner Cabins, 1937 May 13 (Box 29, Folder 167)